DISCOVERING HOW
TO RELAX
YOUR MIND CAN
BE A DAUNTING
TASK BUT IT IS
AN ESSENTIAL
PART OF
MAINTAINING
MENTAL HEALTH
AND WELLBEING
START BY TAKING
SOME TIME OUT
FOR YOURSELF
EACH DAY TO
FOCUS ON
CALMING
ACTIVITIES SUCH
AS YOGA
MEDITATION OR
SIMPLY
LISTENING TO
MUSIC
MAKE SURE YOU
GET ENOUGH
SLEEP EACH
NIGHT AND TRY
TO STICK TO A
REGULAR SLEEP
SCHEDULE
TAKE BREAKS
THROUGHOUT THE
DAY AND
PRACTICE DEEP
BREATHING
EXERCISES WHEN
FEELING
OVERWHELMED OR
STRESSED OUT
LASTLY FIND
WAYS TO REDUCE
STRESS IN YOUR
LIFE SUCH AS
AVOIDING
NEGATIVE PEOPLE
OR SITUATIONS
SETTING
BOUNDARIES WITH
OTHERS AND
ENGAGING IN
POSITIVE
SELF-TALK